Man, he troubled me a lot.
Either that is our car or this or that.
Which that car has given me.  I hope this
car gives better than that.
This time let's buy a car which is a bit rough
and tough.
So let's go and get our new
ship.
Hi Guys.  So it's 11 and 111 right now.
I hope you all have a very good life and
get all the happiness in your life.  And today we are going to do something
very cool.  Today
is Mahashivratri.  So,
Happy Mahashivratri to all of you.  And
guys thank you so much.  Whatever we are going to achieve today is all because
of you guys, your support
and everything is going to happen today because of you people.
So let's go and
start the day.  Only the final touches are left, let's do that.
I thought this is going to be a
special day.  So it is necessary to feel a little special.  Actually,
I just get up and leave like this.
But today I thought a little bit, so let's go now.
So let's go and
you will keep seeing me in this car but
now you will always see me in the next one that is coming.
So let's go and get
our new ship.  Let's go.
[Music]
So hi guys, we're at the showroom and we've
finally arrived to take delivery of our car.
So is this
or that our car or this or that,
you will know in a while.  But
thank you so much guys.  You finally brought
me here today, two years ago, so that
I can take my car myself.
Which I can call my own.  My brother can
call it his own car.  And I am
so proud of myself and my baby and
you guys that you made it possible.  So finally
we are here and I am superduper excited.
Thank you so much.  Thank you very much to
all of you.  And one more thing, we have chosen this car
because we
travel a lot.  So
for the travel, I thought that this time I should take a car
which is a bit rough and tough where
I do not get a chance to think whether
this car can go here or not.
So that's why I chose this car.  So I
hope you guys will like it.  And
you all know that my favourite car is still Fortuner
but it still has some time.  Till then, let
us try driving the smaller baby Fortuner
and see that the XUV
supported us a lot.  I drove it for four years
and in these four years, what all did the XUV not show me.
He has seen everything with me, every struggle of my life, everywhere.
It feels like
a baby or It feels like a baby to me.
He suffered a lot of damage and it
took up a lot of space from me too.
That car saw a lot of things, man.
Whatever happened to me, the same thing happened to him
too.  But still
he never stopped me anywhere.  I never
stopped.  No matter how far I
went, he always brought me back home safely.
And there is
something called love in cars,
you should really do that.  But whatever
that car has given me, I hope this car
gives me better memories than that and we create more good
memories with it.  Ah, XUV will also be at
our house.  Ah, it will be a little different
version of it.  So maybe I think it's
going to change.  There will be some modification etc. in
it.  But we will run that too and
we will definitely run this.  So let's go and find out which car it is.  Let's take
delivery.  So this is what I am doing.  Now there are
₹900 left in these.  You give ₹900.
No problem.  I will give you ₹900.
[laughter]
Done.  If you say it honestly, I have driven the car.   It
became 1 lakh.  [laughter]
He really bothered me here.
[laughter]
I had a fever for three days.  Why did I make such a terrible
booking? We did it two days ago
in this showroom.  The
car was not available at the showroom where we had got it done earlier.  So
we got it here, so we got it done here.
So brother, I got
calls from them, one after the other, one after the other, one after the other.
I said, I have received a call, I will
cancel the train.
I'm so sorry, friend.  I was very high in fever.
And then you know how much a
person gets upset when such calls keep coming.
Paper work done guys.  How many signatures have
we collected?  I mean, after every sign, it's like,
now and now and now and [screaming sound]
we've done at least 20 signs.
Mom,
mom, which car will you take?
Whatever you put your hands on, they will take it.
It is not what
you want, it
is covered.  Ya
no ya no ya
[screaming sound]
no
[music]
[applause]
[screaming sound] nothing more than this
Prem Vayu
this cake Mari Mummy aa this
new car new card give me
clothes give me
clothes didi give me bring clothes give me
clothes
oh
such a big
brother I will eat ok that's it
happy birthday
Panu
Hardik Bhaiya
feed Hardik Bhaiya.
[Music]
Wow new car
M7X you've done it.  It's
on your ventilated seat.  It is in the screen.
From here on the ventilated seat.  Ok?
Ok.
These are your dry modes.  This Mard and
Sand,
we
also have Mard and Sand in it,
yes Mard and Sand,
this thing of running mom, I will
fill some oil in it and
make it in front of you,
if the screen which is in XV is given in Thar
then brother there will be no match for Thar,
then Thar will sell so much, we cannot even imagine it.   Should I turn it off
?   I'm
liking it?   Should I
close the house?   Are
you enjoying it?   Should I
close the house?   Yes, please do it.
Listen, are you feeling good?
Give me the car, Mama I
like it,
this is not our car,
Happy,
this is completely our car, it is
not our car, our car is outside, now this
too is ours,
yes
[crying voice]
alert history ma'am,
he has got the DF filled at 72%, he
should take 72% money too, then this is wrong
thing of yours,
no, with love, with
love, politely,
what happened, why is it not working, if there is a
problem outside, then
why is there a problem,
I have to go out, Mama,
like outside,
we were just checking the features etc., right now
our sunroof is not opening, so we are checking, let's see
why it is not
opening, what is the problem, it
comes.  There is machinery.  This is our mother's
second most favourite car which we are buying.
How are you feeling, mom?   You are
looking great brother.  [laughter]
Will you hang out with me now?
Oh,
tell me where will you go?   If
you go, she will take it.
Mummy said take me to Khatu Shyam ji, take me to
Milpur.  I will not go beyond that.  Then
my buffalo will be left [laughs].   That's
correct.  And more
but it's good.  We took it.  Finally.
Mom was saying for a long time that Pratibha,
you should leave everything.  Take that car,
take that car, so we chose this one.
Clothes.
Yes.
Yes.  We also took money from mom.   There was
some learning issue in the sunroof.
So they corrected it from there onwards.
Now it's working.  It's fine.  I
even opened it two-three times and checked.  So it's
good.  [Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music
] [Music] [Music
]
[Music]
Oh wow Vayu, what is she doing Didi,
now we need Panu Panu for Vayu, Vayu, one by one, a little bit, a little bit for
Mama too, see Panu Didi, she will
apply it for Mama too, oh
come on brother, close your eyes, close your eyes, one two
three, it is applied
[laughs] it doesn't look
crooked,
come inside, let's do the puja
[Music]
Om Shaktimaan,
we are so big,
now we are going to take running shots of our car
because
our team wants perfection.  So let's go and have
some fun.
[music]